

### Contact

+2349098648913

paulrichardevs@gmail.com

Lagos, Nigeria

https://paulrichard.vercel.app/

# **Education**

2018 - 2022

### **Geography & Information System**

University of Ilorin

#### Skills

































# Languages

Yoruba - Native

**English - Fluent** 

### **Interests**

Programming

**M**Gaming

# **Paul Richard**

# Full-Stack Developer

### About

Experienced Full-Stack Developer with a passion for building and creating connected experiences. Skilled in JavaScript (ReactJS),C#, and Asp.Net, with a solid background in MS-SQL and source control. Knowledgeable in Agile software development and web security best practices. Strong communication skills and a team player.

# **Experience**

### <u>The Crox Group</u> - Fullstack.net Developer (Remote)

OCT 2020 - MAR 2022 | Raymond, Ohio

- Work in a Scrum/Agile environment to plan and estimate work at different levels (story, release)
- Develop web applications with robust front and back-ends that work together to track geohazards and warn clients about potential risks
- Correctly implementing Restful webservices and **SOAP Services**
- Create database models to represent complex business entities and relationships
- Implement complex, high-quality, scalable, and extendable end-to-end solutions, using either out-of-the-box or custom functionality

### **SnapX** - FullStack Developer (referred)

DEC 2022 - MAY 2023 | Centerville, Ohio

- Architect, design, develop and deploy scalable enterprise applications for clients, from concept through deployment to production environments
- Good Knowledge of Azure (VPN gateways and express Route) as well as Docker and Kubernetes.
- Demonstrated proficiency with fullstack technologies such as HTML,CSS,JavaScript, Angular, Tailwind, Ajax, and ASP.NET MVC..
- Perform root cause analysis, outline corrective action, and identify mitigation strategies for production issues
- Conduct performance and scalability testing and capacity analysis/planning